{
    "subject": "resource/A_Pistol_Shot",
    "predicate": "ontology/editing",
    "object": "resource/Mario_Serandrei",
    "human_readable": "A Pistol Shot was edited by Mario Serandrei.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9203324913978577,
            "question": "Did Mario Serandrei edit any other films besides A Pistol Shot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8507749438285828,
            "question": "Who edited the film A Pistol Shot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8413090705871582,
            "question": "What film did Mario Serandrei edit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8280637860298157,
            "question": "Name the person who edited the movie A Pistol Shot."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7852113842964172,
            "question": "Can you tell me about a film edited by Mario Serandrei?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7647982239723206,
            "question": "Is Mario Serandrei a director or an editor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7306028604507446,
            "question": "What is the name of the editor for A Pistol Shot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6277638077735901,
            "question": "If you were watching a film called A Pistol Shot, who would you expect to have edited it?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5977750420570374,
            "question": "What is Mario Serandrei known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2872163951396942,
            "question": "What genre is the film A Pistol Shot likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=A Pistol Shot was edited by Mario Serandrei.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2964_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Mario Serandrei known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2964_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you were watching a film called A Pistol Shot, who would you expect to have edited it?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2964_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the editor for A Pistol Shot?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2964_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2964_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that \"Editor: Mario Serandrei\" for the film \"Directed by Luchino Visconti\", which includes \"A Pistol Shot\" in its title. This supports the statement that A Pistol Shot was edited by Mario Serandrei."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}